This is a video demonstrating how to work on ASW.
First, enable admin access so you can access the tool.
After that, open the Ascet tool,
then import the databases that were loaded from TCM.
These are the databases loaded from TCM.
We will take the item name and search for it in the component name section.
After having found the item, check whether the version is correct.
Then create the ATT and a test environment folder for that item.
This step creates the necessary files.
These files are used for the Alinoe tool.
Create the ATT folder for the item,
Then find the missing parameter variables.
Continue searching until all missing Parameters have been found.
Search for the missing Formula after adding the Parameters.
Import the Formula that was exported.
After completing the ATT folder creation step.
Next, we will use the Alinoe tool to create the test design.
Create the necessary files in the ATT folder of the item.
This is required so that GenTestDesign can be used.
After that, fill in the required information fields into the Alinoe tool.
This is needed to generate the test design,
module name, version, sequence number, the folder where the module will be created and the location that contains the test design.
After that, import the DCM file that was exported earlier.
Then run GenTestDesign.
After checking the Min, Max, and Mid fields,
and the necessary information of the variables in the class,
we will search for the missing information
in order to add the Local Parameter variables into Alinoe tool.
Proceed to check the Min, Max, Tolerance values of the input variables.
Proceed to find the missing Min, Max, Mid, and tolerance values for the Imported Parameter variables.
Check whether the formulas of the Local Parameter variables are correct.
After that, proceed to enter the Input.
Write the formula for the Return Value variables.
Then click Generate Test Case to create the test design.
The test design has been created successfully.
After having created the test design, we will create the test cases to cover C0, C1 and MCDC.
Because this test request only requires C0 and C1, we will only create test cases to cover C0 and C1.
This is the basic information tab of the Class.
It includes the review source, tester, and the C0, C1 and MCDC percentages of the Class.
Next, we will import the test cases from the test design into the ATT folder.
We will use the Smart ATT tool to import the test cases from the test design into the ATT folder.
Fill in the required information into the tool so the test cases can be imported.
After importing the test cases into ATT, we will run a trial to check whether the C0, C1 result of the module or item has reached 100%.
These are the test cases that were added from the test design into ATT.
This is the result table showing the C0, C1 and MCDC percentages for the item.
After the result has passed, copy the folder from the ATT_Temp into the workspace folder.
After that, create the PLT folder for the item.
After the PLT folder is created, we will proceed to color the variables.
After coloring for the PLT file is complete, we will send the result to TCM.
As this item does not require MCDC, so for the conditions required for MCDC coverage, we will select the reason as "MCDC is not required".
After that, we will send the result to TCM.
After sending is complete, we will create a walkthrough for the item.
Fill in the required fields in the MCDC tool to create walkthrough.
After filling in all the information in the make walkthrough MCDC tool, we will create walkthrough for the item.
Next is the step of getting the link on TCM.
Currently, after the result has been sent, the status is shown as Complete.
However, UT result has not been uploaded to TCM yet, we can reload the database to check again.
After checking that the version on TCM matches the UT design version that I sent to TCM, we will get the link to create the walkthrough.
Once the walkthrough is created, we will proceed to upload the walkthrough to TCM.